<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><bpd:RefCPIData xmlns:bpd="http://www.treasurydirect.gov/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.treasurydirect.gov/ http://www.treasurydirect.gov/xsd/RefCPI_v1_0_0.xsd">
<REASON>
she loves me
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love her
</REASON>
<REASON>
she cares about me
</REASON>
<REASON>
she makes me laugh
</REASON>
<REASON>
she has the most beautiful eyes
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love spending every second that I can with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
I can always count on her being there for me
</REASON>
<REASON>
I am the happiest when I am  with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
we can talk to each other about anything
</REASON>
<REASON>
who could possibly be a better girlfriend?
</REASON>
<REASON>
I connect with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love her nose
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love her chin
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love her lips
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love her fingers
</REASON>
<REASON>
her fingers interlock perfectly with mine
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love her legs
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love her hair
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is so beautiful
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love the way she smiles at me in the morning
</REASON>
<REASON>
she brightens up my day when I'm with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
we both love food!
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love the feeling of her warmth
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love watching movies with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is the perfect height
</REASON>
<REASON>
she looks so cute when she sleeps next to me in the car
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is the cutest
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love giving her kisses all over her face
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love giving her kisses all over her body
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love singing songs and jamming out with her in the car
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love dancing with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
she can make a mean crepe
</REASON>
<REASON>
the gifts that she give me are given with the utmost thought, care, attention, and love
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is the best lifting buddy
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is the best running buddy
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is so pretty
</REASON>
<REASON>
pusheen reminds me of her (except pusheen is not as cute)
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love cuddling with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is fun to be around
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is so loyal
</REASON>
<REASON>
I will do anything for her
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love taking walks with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love going to the beach with her, even when it's cold and windy
</REASON>
<REASON>
we like the same kinds of music
</REASON>
<REASON>
we both love roller coasters and theme parks
</REASON>
<REASON>
I can't resist being with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
I'm nothing without her
</REASON>
<REASON>
she makes me want to be better
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is so passionate
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is strong (way stronger than she thinks)
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is one of the funniest people I know!
</REASON>
<REASON>
I can't stand being without her
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love rolling around in bed with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love when she plops on top of me
</REASON>
<REASON>
I like her farts
</REASON>
<REASON>
she has a very cute sneeze
</REASON>
<REASON>
she doesn't use the eye guillotine on me
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love waking up to her in the morning
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is all around awesome
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is way smarter than me
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is one of the most intelligent and ambitious people I know
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love when she scratches my head
</REASON>
<REASON>
we are so comfortable with each other
</REASON>
<REASON>
she pops my pimples
</REASON>
<REASON>
she's so HOT
</REASON>
<REASON>
she looks amazing in a dress
</REASON>
<REASON>
she has the best smile
</REASON>
<REASON>
she looks beautiful, even without makeup
</REASON>
<REASON>
we're both pretty weird
</REASON>
<REASON>
she goes out of her way to do things for me
</REASON>
<REASON>
she appreciates my presence
</REASON>
<REASON>
I can't stop thinking about her
</REASON>
<REASON>
she's born in April, my favorite month of the year!
</REASON>
<REASON>
seeing her happy is the best thing ever
</REASON>
<REASON>
we are both kind of OCD sometimes
</REASON>
<REASON>
she reminds me to be clean and wash my hands
</REASON>
<REASON>
she gets me sick packages when I get colds
</REASON>
<REASON>
she has the best Mikey Mouse walk
</REASON>
<REASON>
we can harmonize pretty well together
</REASON>
<REASON>
she puts up with my stupidity
</REASON>
<REASON>
our song is "Clarity" which is the best song ever
</REASON>
<REASON>
we both like when I wear J. Crew
</REASON>
<REASON>
she says good things about me everyday
</REASON>
<REASON>
she loves me, even when I mess up
</REASON>
<REASON>
she made the best cooler ever for formal
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is the best at finding good deals
</REASON>
<REASON>
the best days are chill days with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
we both love sledding
</REASON>
<REASON>
I can't tell her that I love her enough everyday
</REASON>
<REASON>
she sleeps next to me even though I have broad shoulders that take up most of the bed, I snore, I sometimes flail and hit her (accidentally) in my sleep, and I have bad morning breath
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love spending late nights at Ciemas with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love exploring new places with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love walking through the gardens with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love going to awesome concerts with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
she showed me how to get the most out of eating escargot by putting bread in the garlic left in the little bowls
</REASON>
<REASON>
she believes in me
</REASON>
<REASON>
she stays by me, even when things get difficult
</REASON>
<REASON>
I want to give her everything in the world
</REASON>
<REASON>
we have amazing trips together to new cities
</REASON>
<REASON>
it is so easy to come up with at least 100 reasons why I love her
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love kissing her when she least expects it
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love how we can be derpy together
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love finding any reason to celebrate with you
</REASON>
<REASON>
our photobooth sessions are legendarily cute
</REASON>
<REASON>
she makes the best meals ever
</REASON>
<REASON>
the chocolate covered strawberries she made for me were amazing
</REASON>
<REASON>
giving her piggyback rides lets me hold her and  stay in shape at the same time!
</REASON>
<REASON>
I can't think of anyone else I would rather be with
</REASON>
<REASON>
our daily Skype sessions keep me going
</REASON>
<REASON>
she got me the cutest NY monkey
</REASON>
<REASON>
we are both intrigued by all the weird facts at the Ripley's Believe It or Not museum
</REASON>
<REASON>
she likes the pretzels and not the brown chips in Chex Mix but I like the brown chips and not the pretzels. We were meant to be.
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love holding her hands in mine
</REASON>
<REASON>
we are both asian :)
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love getting midnight snacks at McDonalds/Red Mango with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love wrapping my arms around her to keep her warm when it's cold outside
</REASON>
<REASON>
we listen to each other's music on soundcloud
</REASON>
<REASON>
she understands that macs are wayyyyyyy better than pcs
</REASON>
<REASON>
I'm always excited to talk to her
</REASON>
<REASON>
just seeing her face and hearing her voice brightens up my day
</REASON>
<REASON>
she loves me even when I wear white long pants
</REASON>
<REASON>
she loves me even when I dress annoyingly preppy
</REASON>
<REASON>
she loves me even though I'm OCD
</REASON>
<REASON>
she has helped me mature and become more responsible
</REASON>
<REASON>
she inspires me to live passionately
</REASON>
<REASON>
we both really enjoy eating tapas
</REASON>
<REASON>
trips with her are the best vacations
</REASON>
<REASON>
she actually enjoys popping my pimples and cleaning my face
</REASON>
<REASON>
we love eating sour gummy worms together
</REASON>
<REASON>
she gets my stupid jokes :)
</REASON>
<REASON>
her chocolate chip banana bread is to die for
</REASON>
<REASON>
we are extremely classy on our dates
</REASON>
<REASON>
she makes the best selections for dim sum
</REASON>
<REASON>
I'm always excited to be with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
she manages to warm me up even on the coldest days
</REASON>
<REASON>
she likes my cheesiness
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is so good at cooking, especially fried rice!
</REASON>
<REASON>
I can't stop smiling when I'm with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is the best person to have on a road trip hands down
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is confident and capable
</REASON>
<REASON>
she can do anything she puts her mind onto
</REASON>
<REASON>
she's always looking out for me (and I'm always looking out for her!)
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love telling her corny random facts every morning (hopefully it brightens up her day a bit)!
</REASON>
<REASON>
we were probably meant to be together by some celestial phenomenon
</REASON>
<REASON>
I try to dress up for her whenever I can
</REASON>
<REASON>
seeing her face puts me in a better mood no matter what kind of day I had
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is just the best
</REASON>
<REASON>
she pushes me to work harder
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love hugging her at random times during our study sessions
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is a good listener and the first person I tell any news to
</REASON>
<REASON>
she wears the cutest summer dresses
</REASON>
<REASON>
she has a very extensive knowledge of romantic comedies that I have embarrassingly come to enjoy
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is always excited to see me
</REASON>
<REASON>
she hangs out with me even when I get sick
</REASON>
<REASON>
all my best and most memorable times in college have been with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
the only reason why we'd break up is because we want every day to be like our first
</REASON>
<REASON>
we both appreciate the pictures we send each other of awesome food we have
</REASON>
<REASON>
I'm always eager to try new things with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
she gives the best massages
</REASON>
<REASON>
she knows exactly what to send me in a care package
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love taking little walks with her whenever I can (i.e. going to vondee/BC during study breaks and picking up delivery from Telecom Dr.)
</REASON>
<REASON>
she's my girlfriend and best friend
</REASON>
<REASON>
even though we're hundreds of miles apart during the summer, she still takes the time to spend time talking to me and hearing about my days
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is my little New Yorker
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is my little Greco Gekko
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is my little fashionista
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is my little bugabee
</REASON>
<REASON>
we dominate the clown game at frankies together
</REASON>
<REASON>
I love trying out new restaurants with her
</REASON>
<REASON>
she is so sweet and genuine
</REASON>
</bpd:RefCPIData>
